{
  "PCOD": {
    "Level1": [
      {
        "question": "What is the focus of Lt. Col. Dr. Kim Hopkins' postdoctoral training mentioned in the content?",
        "options": [
          "Studying Polycystic Ovary Syndrome",
          "Conducting research on diabetes",
          "Developing a new medical treatment",
          "Exploring cardiovascular diseases"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Studying Polycystic Ovary Syndrome"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who are the special volunteers acknowledged for their role in compiling the information in the booklet?",
        "options": [
          "Dr. Samia Noursi and Lt. Col. Dr. Kim Hopkins",
          "Nathan Dinh and Bani Saluja",
          "University of Richmond and University of Maryland",
          "Dr. Kim Hopkins and Dr. Samia Noursi"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Nathan Dinh and Bani Saluja"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which section of the booklet can health care providers and researchers find further information about PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "Section V",
          "Section VI",
          "Section IV",
          "Section VII"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Section VI"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the key methods used to define and diagnose PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "Blood test only",
          "Combination of signs and symptoms",
          "Genetic testing",
          "Physical examination only"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Combination of signs and symptoms"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the provided content, what percentage of women with PCOS are estimated to remain undiagnosed in primary care?",
        "options": [
          "Less than 30%",
          "At least 70%",
          "Around 50%",
          "Over 90%"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "At least 70%"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which medical journal is mentioned in the content as a reference for screening for diabetes and cardiometabolic disease in women with PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "The Lancet",
          "The New England Journal of Medicine",
          "The British Journal of Diabetes & Vascular Disease",
          "The Journal of Clinical Endocrinology & Metabolism"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The British Journal of Diabetes & Vascular Disease"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is PCOS primarily defined by?",
        "options": [
          "Hyperandrogenism",
          "Presence of ovarian cysts",
          "Ovarian dysfunction",
          "Polycystic ovarian morphology"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hyperandrogenism"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many diagnostic criteria are required to define PCOS according to the Rotterdam criteria?",
        "options": [
          "3",
          "2",
          "1",
          "4"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which organization endorsed the Rotterdam criteria for PCOS in 2012?",
        "options": [
          "American Society for Reproductive Medicine (ASRM)",
          "National Institutes of Health (NIH)",
          "European Society of Human Reproduction and Embryology (ESHRE)",
          "Androgen Excess and PCOS Society (AE-PCOS)"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "European Society of Human Reproduction and Embryology (ESHRE)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term for the condition characterized by the complete absence of menstruation?",
        "options": [
          "Amenorrhea",
          "Oligomenorrhea",
          "Menorrhagia",
          "Menstrual Disorders"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Amenorrhea"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are some of the health implications associated with PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "Psychological issues only",
          "Metabolic issues only",
          "Dermatological issues only",
          "Reproductive issues only"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Metabolic issues only"
      },
      {
        "question": "What can be observed in a transvaginal ultrasound of a woman with PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "Normal ovary and enlarged uterus",
          "Polycystic ovaries and normal uterus",
          "Enlarged ovary and excessive follicles",
          "Excessive follicles and enlarged uterus"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Enlarged ovary and excessive follicles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which area of a woman's life is NOT affected by PCOS according to the content?",
        "options": [
          "Sleep",
          "Reproductive health",
          "Dermatological health",
          "Metabolic health"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sleep"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main marker for diagnosing PCOS in adolescents?",
        "options": [
          "Hyperandrogenemia",
          "Hirsutism",
          "Irregular menstrual cycles",
          "Endometrial cancer"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Hyperandrogenemia"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary issue for women at reproductive ages with PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "Acne",
          "Fertility issues",
          "Menstrual irregularity",
          "Breast cancer risk"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fertility issues"
      },
      {
        "question": "What health risk is significantly increased in older women with PCOS compared to those without PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "Diabetes",
          "Ovarian cancer",
          "Endometrial cancer",
          "Breast cancer"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Diabetes"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can women potentially reduce the risk of aggravating PCOS symptoms related to diet?",
        "options": [
          "Limiting inflammatory foods like dairy products and foods high in glycemic load",
          "Eating more gluten-containing foods",
          "Increasing consumption of sugary desserts",
          "Avoiding all dairy products"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Limiting inflammatory foods like dairy products and foods high in glycemic load"
      },
      {
        "question": "When do endocrine-disrupting chemicals pose the greatest risk for female reproductive health issues, including PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "During menopause",
          "During adolescence",
          "During prenatal and early postnatal development",
          "During adulthood"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "During prenatal and early postnatal development"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the lifestyle changes recommended for managing PCOS symptoms?",
        "options": [
          "Consuming foods, trans fats, and saturated fats",
          "Increasing smoking habits",
          "Eating a high-fiber, low-sugar diet with lots of vegetables, whole grains, and fruits",
          "Avoiding daily physical activity"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Eating a high-fiber, low-sugar diet with lots of vegetables, whole grains, and fruits"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which medication is suggested for managing PCOS symptoms related to hirsutism, acne, and difficulty conceiving?",
        "options": [
          "Lipid-lowering agents",
          "Inositol supplement",
          "Metformin",
          "Low-androgen oral contraceptives"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Inositol supplement"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the economic impacts associated with PCOS treatment?",
        "options": [
          "Cost of treating type 2 diabetes",
          "Cost of treating osteoporosis",
          "Cost of treating hypertension",
          "Cost of treating common cold"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cost of treating type 2 diabetes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the critical gaps remaining in the understanding of PCOS mentioned in the content?",
        "options": [
          "Connections of comorbidities to PCOS",
          "Prevalence of PCOS in different age groups",
          "Treatment options for PCOS",
          "Effects of PCOS on men's health"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Connections of comorbidities to PCOS"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which organization mentioned in the content is a nonprofit support and advocacy organization for women and girls with polycystic ovary syndrome?",
        "options": [
          "American Society for Reproductive Medicine",
          "PCOS Challenge: The National Polycystic Ovary Syndrome Association",
          "Androgen Excess and PCOS Society",
          "American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "PCOS Challenge: The National Polycystic Ovary Syndrome Association"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the serious effects that women with PCOS are at higher risk for, as mentioned in the content?",
        "options": [
          "Mental health disorders such as anxiety and depression",
          "Vision problems",
          "Bone fractures",
          "Skin rashes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mental health disorders such as anxiety and depression"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the term for the absence of a woman's monthly menstrual period?",
        "options": [
          "Cardiovascular disease",
          "Amenorrhea",
          "Androgen",
          "Cyst"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Amenorrhea"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which hormone promotes the development and maintenance of male sex characteristics?",
        "options": [
          "Estrogen",
          "Dyslipidemia",
          "Androgen",
          "Etiology"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Androgen"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does dyslipidemia refer to?",
        "options": [
          "Problems with the heart and blood vessels",
          "Absence of menstrual period",
          "High levels of lipids in the blood",
          "A closed, saclike pocket of tissue"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "High levels of lipids in the blood"
      }
    ],
    "Level2": [
      {
        "question": "The presence of excessive _________ on various parts of the body is a common symptom of PCOS.",
        "options": [
          "hair",
          "muscle",
          "skin elasticity",
          "bone density"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "hair"
      },
      {
        "question": "PCOS is often associated with an increased risk of _________.",
        "options": [
          "infertility",
          "hypertension",
          "skin cancer",
          "hair loss"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "infertility"
      },
      {
        "question": "Women with PCOS may have a higher incidence of _________ due to insulin resistance.",
        "options": [
          "diabetes",
          "anemia",
          "thrombosis",
          "hypothyroidism"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "diabetes"
      },
      {
        "question": "A common treatment for managing PCOS symptoms includes lifestyle changes such as improved diet and _________.",
        "options": [
          "exercise",
          "sun exposure",
          "meditation",
          "supplement intake"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "exercise"
      },
      {
        "question": "_________ metabolic abnormalities caused by PCOS that increase the risk of type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease.",
        "options": [
          "Increased abdominal fat and insulin resistance",
          "High muscle mass and decreased cholesterol",
          "Low blood pressure and high protein intake",
          "Increased calcium absorption and decreased glucose levels"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Increased abdominal fat and insulin resistance"
      },
      {
        "question": "__________ recommended by the CDC to manage PCOS symptoms?",
        "options": [
          "150 minutes of moderate-intensity exercise per week",
          "30 minutes of vigorous exercise daily",
          "200 minutes of light exercise monthly",
          "75 minutes of high-intensity exercise weekly"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "150 minutes of moderate-intensity exercise per week"
      }
    ]
  },
  "Diabetics": {
    "Level1": [
      {
        "question": "Which medical journal is mentioned in the content as a reference for screening for diabetes and cardiometabolic disease in women with PCOS?",
        "options": [
          "The Lancet",
          "The New England Journal of Medicine",
          "The British Journal of Diabetes & Vascular Disease",
          "The Journal of Clinical Endocrinology & Metabolism"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The British Journal of Diabetes & Vascular Disease"
      }
    ],
    "Level2": [
      {
        "question": "Women with PCOS may have a higher incidence of _________ due to insulin resistance.",
        "options": [
          "diabetes",
          "anemia",
          "thrombosis",
          "hypothyroidism"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "diabetes"
      },
      {
        "question": "__________ metabolic abnormalities caused by PCOS that increase the risk of type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease.",
        "options": [
          "Increased abdominal fat and insulin resistance",
          "High muscle mass and decreased cholesterol",
          "Low blood pressure and high protein intake",
          "Increased calcium absorption and decreased glucose levels"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Increased abdominal fat and insulin resistance"
      }
    ]
  },
  "General": {
    "Level1": [
    {
      "question": "What is the common term used for the sensation of a baby moving inside the womb?",
      "options": [
        "Flutter",
        "Kick",
        "Wiggle",
        "Twist"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kick"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many weeks does a full-term pregnancy typically last?",
      "options": [
        "36 weeks",
        "38 weeks",
        "40 weeks",
        "42 weeks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "40 weeks"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name for the phenomenon where some women experience nausea and vomiting during pregnancy?",
      "options": [
        "Morning Sickness",
        "Nighttime Nausea",
        "All-day Sickness",
        "Pregnancy Blues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Morning Sickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "During which trimester does the baby develop fingerprints?",
      "options": [
        "First trimester",
        "Second trimester",
        "Third trimester",
        "After birth"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Second trimester"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for the fluid-filled sac that surrounds and protects the developing baby in the womb?",
      "options": [
        "Amniotic sac",
        "Placenta",
        "Umbilical cord",
        "Embryo pouch"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Amniotic sac"
    },
    {
      "question": "What percentage of babies are born on their actual due date?",
      "options": [
        "10%",
        "25%",
        "50%",
        "75%"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "10%"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the common term for the line that may appear on a pregnant woman's belly due to hormonal changes?",
      "options": [
        "Pregnancy line",
        "Belly stripe",
        "Stretch mark",
        "Linea nigra"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Linea nigra"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the medical term for giving birth to twins?",
      "options": [
        "Bifurcation",
        "Dual birth",
        "Twinning",
        "Twins delivery"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Twinning"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the average weight gain recommended during pregnancy for a woman of normal weight?",
      "options": [
        "10-15 pounds",
        "20-30 pounds",
        "30-40 pounds",
        "50-60 pounds"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "25-35 pounds"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which month is celebrated as National Pregnancy Awareness Month?",
      "options": [
        "March",
        "May",
        "September",
        "December"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "May"
    }
  ],
    "Level2": [
    {
      "question": "_______ is the most common pregnancy craving reported by women.",
      "options": [
        "Pickles and ice cream",
        "Chocolate and peanut butter",
        "Spicy foods",
        "Fruit and yogurt"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pickles and ice cream"
    },
    {
      "question": "Number of bones in a newborn baby's body is _______.",
      "options": [
        "150",
        "206",
        "270",
        "300"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "206"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ is a common term for a baby born before 37 weeks of pregnancy.",
      "options": [
        "Term baby",
        "Preterm baby",
        "Full-term baby",
        "Late-term baby"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Preterm baby"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ is the term for a pregnancy complication characterized by high blood pressure and signs of damage to another organ system, most often the liver and kidneys.",
      "options": [
        "Preeclampsia",
        "Gestational diabetes",
        "Hyperemesis gravidarum",
        "Ectopic pregnancy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Preeclampsia"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ is important for preventing neural tube defects when taken before and during early pregnancy.",
      "options": [
        "Vitamin A",
        "Vitamin B12",
        "Vitamin C",
        "Folic acid"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Folic acid"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ is the term for the process of the baby descending into the pelvis in preparation for birth.",
      "options": [
        "Fetal rotation",
        "Pelvic engagement",
        "Cervical dilation",
        "Crowning"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pelvic engagement"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ hormone is often referred to as the 'pregnancy hormone' and is responsible for maintaining pregnancy and preparing the body for childbirth.",
      "options": [
        "Estrogen",
        "Progesterone",
        "Testosterone",
        "Prolactin"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Progesterone"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ is the term for the thick, yellowish fluid that a baby passes during the first few days after birth, rich in antibodies and nutrients.",
      "options": [
        "Colostrum",
        "Mucus plug",
        "Meconium",
        "Lanugo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Colostrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ position is considered the optimal fetal position for birth.",
      "options": [
        "Breech",
        "Transverse",
        "Occiput posterior",
        "Vertex"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Vertex"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ is the term for the process of the uterus returning to its normal size and position after childbirth.",
      "options": [
        "Involution",
        "Regression",
        "Contraction",
        "Restoration"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Involution"
    }
  ]
  }
}